This little piggy came home...
Berkshire County is a horror, thriller film directed by Audrey Cummings.
Kylie Winters, a bullied and self-loathing teen, reluctantly agrees to
babysit at an isolated country mansion on Halloween night.
When a small boy in a pig mask appears at the door trick-or-treating, Kylie's
night transforms into a horrifying and violent cat-and-mouse game.
She must go beyond what she ever thought possible if she
and the children are to survive the night.
Kylie Winters, played by Alysa King.
Phoebe, played by Madison Ferguson.
Roberta, played by Samora Smallwood.
Swine, played by Bart Rochon.
Marcus, played by Aaron Chartrand.
Sam, played by Christophe Gallander.
Berkshire (  BARK-sheer, -⁠shər; abbreviated Berks.), officially the Royal
County of Berkshire, is a ceremonial county in South East England.
It is bordered by Oxfordshire to the north, Buckinghamshire to the north-east, Greater London to the
east, Surrey to the south-east, Hampshire to the south, and Wiltshire to the west.
Reading is the largest settlement and the county town.
The county has an area of 1,263 km2 (488 sq mi) and a population of 911,403.
The population is concentrated in the east, the area closest to Greater London, which includes the county's
largest towns: Reading (174,224), Slough (164,793), Bracknell (113,205), and Maidenhead (70,374).
The west is rural, and its largest town is Newbury (33,841).
For local government purposes Berkshire comprises six unitary authority areas: Bracknell
Forest, Reading, Slough, West Berkshire, Windsor and Maidenhead, and Wokingham.
The historic county included the parts of Oxfordshire south of the River Thames,
which formed its northern border, but excluded Caversham and Slough.
The Berkshire Downs, a chalk downland and area of outstanding
natural beauty, occupy the west of the county.
They are the source of the River Kennet, which flows east
through Newbury before meeting the Thames at Reading.
The Thames then forms Berkshire's northern border, flowing past Maidenhead,
before entering the county and flowing past Slough and Windsor.
The south-east of the county contains Swinley Forest, a remnant of
Windsor Forest now used as a forestry plantation.
There is evidence of prehistoric settlement on the Berkshire Downs,
including the Iron Age Uffington White Horse, now in Oxfordshire.
In the Anglo-Saxon period the region was contested by Mercia and Wessex, and
Alfred the Great was born in Wantage, also now in Oxfordshire.
Windsor Castle, which would become the official country residence of the
British monarch, was built after the Norman Conquest.
The county has been the site of several battles, particularly during the First English Civil War, when
Reading and Wallingford were besieged two battles took place at Newbury, in 1643 and 1644.
The proximity of the east of the county to London led to development from the nineteenth century,
when Slough became an industrial centre and Bracknell was designated a new town.
Software development and high-tech industry dominate the economy in
the east, but the west remains an agricultural region.
The film explores themes of high school, halloween,
babysitter, home invasion, pig mask.
The tone is dark and intense.